

CONTACT ME AT

- Binong 1 Residence block F11
- ahauwlie@gmail.com
- (+62) 895-1405-5817
- github/gitlab: ahauwlie

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• HTML/CSS
- •••• SQL
- ••• Python
- ••• C/C++
- •••• PHP
- •••• Java

BAYU TIRTA SARTAMA

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a final level Computer Science student at Multimedia Nusantara University. I like to make projects on web design and mobile applications. I always try to learn from experience to improve the abilities and knowledge that I have.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DESIGN

Skynine coffee | Oct 2018

INTERNSHIP

Merah Putih media | Jan 2019 - May 2019

- re-create the website and change the framework from Wordpress to Laravel
- create a mobile application for "Kabaroto"

MUSIC COACH

SMAN 11 Tangerang | Jan 2015 - Present

• I will share my expertise with my student to help them overcome any musical hurdle they're dealing with. They can play piano, discuss musical issues, and get help from me on practicing and learning music.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

SMAN 11 TANGERANG

Semi Military School | 2012 - 2015

Science major

MULTIMEDIA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY

2015 - Present

- Oracle database administrator
- Gpa 2.9